ltdcommodities.com 2019-02-21

# None

#### Item(s) added to your shopping cart.

#### Enjoy $5 Shipping on $50 When You Sign Up for Emails

#### Enjoy $5 Shipping on $50 When You Sign Up for Emails

### Sign Up & Save! Be the first to hear about special promotional offers, new product arrivals and limited-time sales.

### Sign Up & Save! Be the first to hear about special promotional offers, new product arrivals and limited-time sales.

*Orders of $50 or more. Valid for new subscribers only.

*Orders of $50 or more. Valid for new subscribers only.

Privacy Statement We will never sell your email address. To learn more read our Privacy Policy.

#### We already have you on our List.

#### We already have you on our List.

### Thank you for confirming your subscription! 

### Thank you for confirming your subscription! 

Continue Shopping

We will never sell your email address. To learn more read our Privacy Policy.

#### Thank you for signing up for LTD emails!

#### Thank you for signing up for LTD emails!

### Check your inbox for your exclusive discount and start shopping TODAY!

### Check your inbox for your exclusive discount and start shopping TODAY!

Continue Shopping

We will never sell your email address. To learn more read our Privacy Policy.

##  Privacy Policy

LTD Commodities LLC holds the privacy and security of our customers in the highest regard. The following data explains what kind of information is gathered on the LTD Commodities website and how the information is used.

LTD Commodities LLC will treat your email address as confidential information; we will not rent, sell or trade the contents of our email list to any outside parties.

**Does LTD Commodities offer secure online ordering?**

Yes, we do. All customer and order information is securely stored behind a firewall and protected from unauthorized access. Your online session is encrypted using SSL with a certificate provided by Verisign. Therefore, none of your personal information, including credit card number, name and address, can be read as the information travels over the internet. Your credit card number is protected by our encryption methods as soon as we capture it and before it is stored in our database to protect it from potential theft. LTD Commodities does not store your CVV2 credit card security code anywhere on its system.

**What do you do with my email address?**

LTD Commodities LLC collects your email address as part of your registration with us. We use this address to communicate with you about your account. We do not sell your email address to others.

**What kind of information do you collect from me when I visit your web site?**

We do not collect any personally identifiable information from those merely visiting our site. We do ask for additional information if you would like to place an order, request an order status or a free catalog, or if you need to communicate with us regarding an account issue.

**What are 'cookies' and how do you use them?**

"Cookies" are files that are stored on your device's hard drive by your web browser and are used to improve your online experience. Cookies help us identify account holders and optimize their shopping experience by allowing functions such as online shopping carts. Accepting cookies through your web browser is your personal choice. You can set your browser to disable cookies.

However, if you choose not to accept cookies, we may not be able to provide you with as good of an experience as one that is specifically tailored to your needs by utilizing the cookie.

We may also use technologies, such as our own cookies, to provide you with personalized online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of our cookies used for this online advertising, [click here](http://dtmc.ltdcommodities.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=2846&cname=LTD%20Commodities&cmagic=eb9fc3&clogo=LTD_logo.png&loc=us&lang=en-us). We may use the services of third parties to collect and use anonymous information about your visits to and interactions with our website through the use of technologies such as cookies to personalize advertisements for goods and services. To learn more, or to opt-out of receiving advertisements tailored to your interests by our third party partners, visit the Network Advertising Initiative at [www.networkadvertising.org/choices](https://networkadvertising.org/choices). 

**Does LTD share information it collects from me with outside parties?**

The information you provided on the website is used to fulfill a product order, a catalog request or research a customer inquiry. The information that you provide is stored in-house separate from the Internet.

We do occasionally share name and address information with other catalog companies that offer similar products. We will not share any personal financial information. If you are on our catalog mailing list, or order from one of our catalogs, and would prefer not to have your name shared with other catalog companies, please email at **MarketingDepartment@ltdcommodities.com** and ask that your name not be shared.

From time to time, we may modify or amend this privacy and security policy in order to comply with new laws or regulations or to reflect future changes in our business practices. All such modifications and amendments to the privacy and security policy shall be posted here in the Customer Service section of www.ltdcommodities.com. The current policy has been in effect since April 2015.

**How else do you use information about my company?**

Once you make a purchase from us, your company becomes a part of our customer file. As a valued LTD Commodities customer, we will add you to our mailing list to receive future catalogs and offers.

**How do I remove my company name from LTD's mailing lists?**

 Contact us by email, mail or fax and we will remove you from our mailing list. Please include the company account number, company name and address, and your name and title.

**How can I contact LTD?**

  |  **Email:** |  Click Here to contact us via email.  
   
---|---|---  
  |  **Telephone:** |  Order Department (847) 295-5532  
Customer Service (847) 295-6058

Our office hours are:  
Monday - Friday  
7:00am - 8:00pm  
Central Time

  |  **Fax:** |  (847) 604-7600  
   
  |  **Address:** |  LTD Commodities LLC, 2800 Lakeside Drive, Bannockburn, IL 60015  

**Amendments to our Privacy Policy**

If we amend our Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on our website for your review.

#### Special Offers

* * *

x

## Mobile Terms and Conditions

Effective Date: 02/07/2018

When you opt-in to the service, we will send you a message to confirm your signup. Text **JOIN** to **57531** to receive **LTD Promotional Messaging! Message and data rates may apply. You will receive up to 6 messages per month.** Text **"HELP"** for help. Text **"STOP"** to cancel.

**STOP Information**

You can cancel this service at any time. Just text **"STOP"** to **57531**. After you send the message **"STOP"** to us, we will send you a reply message to confirm that you have been unsubscribed. After this, you will no longer receive LTD Promotional Messages from us.

**HELP Information**

If at any time you forget what keywords are supported, just text **"HELP"** to **57531**. After you send the message **"HELP"** to us, we will respond with instructions on how to use our service as well as how to unsubscribe.

**Supported carriers are:**

AT&T, Verizon Wireless, Sprint, T-Mobile®, U.S. Cellular, Boost Mobile, MetroPCS, Virgin Mobile, Alaska Communications Systems (ACS), Appalachian Wireless (EKN), Bluegrass Cellular, Cellular One of East Central, IL (ECIT), Cellular One of Northeast Pennsylvania, Cricket, Coral Wireless (Mobi PCS), COX, Cross, Element Mobile (Flat Wireless), Epic Touch (Elkhart Telephone), GCI, Golden State, Hawkeye (Chat Mobility), Hawkeye (NW Missouri), Illinois Valley Cellular, Inland Cellular, iWireless (Iowa Wireless), Keystone Wireless (Immix Wireless/PC Man), Mosaic (Consolidated or CTC Telecom), Nex-Tech Wireless, NTelos, Panhandle Communications, Pioneer, Plateau (Texas RSA 3 Ltd), Revol, RINA, Simmetry (TMP Corporation), Thumb Cellular, Union Wireless, United Wireless, Viaero Wireless, and West Central (WCC or 5 Star Wireless).

T-Mobile is not liable for delayed or undelivered messages.

As always, message and data rates may apply for any messages sent to you from us and to us from you. If you have any questions about your text plan or data plan, it is best to contact your wireless provider.

For all questions about the services provided by this short code, you can send an email to [service@ltdcommodities.com](mailto:service@ltdcommodities.com)

We take your privacy seriously. Please visit Privacy Policy to review our privacy policy.

#### Your session will time out in 

* * *
